My husband passed away of COVID two years ago.
I'm
also raising a grandson and taking care of my 90-year-old mom
that we moved here from the Twin Cities.
So in the process of my husband passing,
uh,
my grandson had to get on different insurance.
We've looked around,
looked around,
got him on different insurance,
and,
um,
started coming here.
I wanted to be able to come with him.
We use the,
uh,
dental.
And it has been,
it's been an amazing experience,
you know,
you have the health care,
you have the quick care,
you know,
you have the dental care.
I know there's mental health care here,
and I think
that is very
impactful for our community.
We all need this in our community.